SHU-KUANG LIN

M 347-425-6738

E shukuanglin@gmail.com

W shukuanglin.com

I am a talented interactive artist, visual director, and UX/UI designer. In 7 years of professional experience, I have taken an interdisciplinary approach to all of my creative endeavors, whether they are web, film, visual design, motion pictures, UX/UI, and interactive media. I look forward to exploring different topics and using my strength to create phenomenal experiences for users and participants.

WORK EXPERIENCE

TIAA

Designer 01/2016 – present

- Responsive design thinking on multiple digital platforms
- UX/UI design for potential personal financial portal

Rozilo, Inc.

Lead UX/UI Designer

05/2012 - 12/2015

- Front-end web design with CSS, HTML5
- Design UX/UI for both iOS and Android
- Responsive design thinking from web form to mobile app

xXtraLab Design CO. LTD.

Senior Interactive Designer

- 06/2010 07/2011
- Manage motion graphics, animation and user interactive behavior
- Lead the main visual design and user experience for each project
- Design user interfaces for diverse interactive installations

BanZig Design

Front-end Web Designer

04/2009 - 07/2010

- Design website layout, graphic design and flash animated website
- Motion website and Wordpress theme are my specialty

EDUCATION

Pratt Institute

MFA in Digital Art, Interactive Art

09/2011 - 05/2013

Yuan Ze University

BA in Communication Design, Digital Media Design

08/2003 - 06/2007

SKILLS AND EXPERTISE

Tools/Softwares

Adobe Creative Cloud, AfterEffects, Final Cut Pro, OmniGraffle, Chrome Inspector, Sketch, Invision App, Max/MSP

Knowledge/Skills/Abilities

Wireframing, HTML5, CSS, Javascript, Wordpress, UX/UI, User Flow Design, iOS, Android, Responsive Design, Web Layout, Polished Visual Theme, Interactive Art, Motion Graphic, Projection Mapping

AWARDS AND EXHIBITION

The Present is The Past

Pratt Digital Art Gallery in Brooklyn

May, 2013

Interactive Installation

2010 International Flora Exposition-Celebrity's House

The TID Gold Award of 2010 Taiwan Interior Design Award

2010

Interactive Installation

The Chaser

The Gold Award of The 4th Digital Art Festival

2009

Animation

LANGUAGES

Mandarin/English